Guide to the Anna Fuller Fund Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Anna Fuller Fund Records, Accession 1988-A-094
  - Anna Fuller Grants, Series II
    - # 406 Susan L. Swain: Declined, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 297)
    - # 407 J.G. Georgatsos, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 298)
    - # 408 James K. McDougall: Declined, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 299)
    - # 409 Teh-sheng Chan, 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 300)
    - # 410 Andrzej Kahl, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 301)
    - # 411 Keith Burridge, 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 302)
    - # 412 Lauren H. Sompayrac, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 303)
    - # 413 Ronald R. Wright, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 304)
    - # 414 Ruth Kevenoff, 1973-1977 (Box 29, Folder 305)
    - # 415 Steven Wright, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 306-307)
    - # 416 Robert Grainger: Declined, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 308)
    - # 417 Ellen Schneider: Declined, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 309)
    - # 418 Frances Jurnak, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 310)
    - # 419 Mark Meuth, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 311)
    - # 420 Raymond Poon, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 312)
    - # 421 Elizabeth Blackburn, 1974-1978 (Box 30, Folder 313)
    - # 422 J. Claude Heunier, 1974-1977 (Box 30, Folder 314)
    - # 423 Gregory Hundy, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 315)
    - # 424 Daniel S. Straus, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 316)
    - # 425 Alfred Bothwell, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 317)
    - # 426 William Snell, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 318)
    - # 427 Carole Mikoryak, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 319)
    - # 428 Jeffrey Bluestone, 1979-1981 (Box 31, Folder 320)
    - # 430 W. Michael Kuehl, 1974-1977 (Box 31, Folder 321)
    - # 431 Martin D. Schehter, 1974-1977 (Box 31, Folder 322)
    - # 432 John Bedbrook, 1974-1977 (Box 31, Folder 323)
    - # 433 Robert L. Clark, 1974-1979 (Box 31, Folder 324)
    - # 434 Eli Canaan!: Declined, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 325)
    - # 435 Agnes Schonbrunn: Declined, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 326)
    - # 436 Timothy A. Springer: Declined, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 327)
    - # 437 Virginia Zakian: Declined, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 328)
    - # 438 Klaus D. Eigert, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 329)
    - William Clark Taylor, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 330)
    - # 439 Robert Humphreys, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 331)
    - # 440 Paul Saluk, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 332)
    - # 441 David Kahack: Declined, 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 333)
    - # 442 Steven Humphries, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 334)
    - # 443 Robert Margolis, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 335)
    - # 444 Maurice C. Kemp, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 336)
    - # 445 Susan Rick Wei, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 337)
    - # 446 Sister Mary Jenkins, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 338)
    - # 447 John La Badie, 1975-1978 (Box 32, Folder 339)
    - # 448 Motowo Tomita, 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 340)
    - # 449 Peter V. Tishler, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 341)
    - # 450 David Shur: Declined, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 342)
    - # 451 Sylvia Hu: Declined, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 343)
    - # 452 Salk Institute Charles Birdwell: Declined, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 344)
    - # 453 Cornell University David Tu: Declined, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 345)
    - # 454 Dean Hammer: Declined, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 346)
    - # 455 Jamea Kurnick: Declined, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 347)
    - # 456 David Steffen: Declined, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 348)
    - # 457 Richard Tyhach: Declined, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 349)
    - # 458 Jan Maisel: Declined, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 350)
    - # 459 Yale University Kurt Stenn, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 351)
    - # 460 Gerald Reeck, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 352)
    - # 461 Harry Orr: Declined, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 353)
    - # 462 Mary Lou King, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 354)
    - # 463 Patricia Maness, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 355)
    - # 464 C.A. Kozak, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 356)
    - # 465 Ephraim Lavie, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 357)
    - # 466 Francis Kolpack, 1976-1979 (Box 34, Folder 358)
    - # 467 James Hanley, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 359)
    - # 468 David Grant, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 360)
    - # 469 Perry Hackett, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 361)
    - # 470 Heinz Furthmayr, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 362)
    - # 471 Robert Carroll, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 363)
    - # 472 Michael Clemens, 1976-1978 (Box 34, Folder 364)
    - # 473 Jose Melero, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 365)
    - # 474 Janis Vincent, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 366)
    - # 475 Lu-Hal Wang: Declined, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 367)
    - # 476 Daniel Beneski, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 368)
    - # 477 Basth Deepak, 1977-1978 (Box 35, Folder 369)
    - # 479 Stephen Turner, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 370)
    - # 480 Robert F. Gagel, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 371)
    - # 481 David Hoscstelli, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 372)
    - # 482 J. Douglas Waterfield, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 373)
    - # 483 Evelyn Karson, 1974-1977 (Box 36, Folder 374)
    - # 484 John C. Fiddes, 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 375)
    - # 485 Kevin McEntee, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 376)
    - # 486 Jonathan Logan, 1976-1980 (Box 36, Folder 377)
    - # 487 Lawrence Honig, 1977-1979 (Box 36, Folder 378)
    - # 488 Ronald Hoffman, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 379)
    - # 489 Curtis Harper, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 380)
    - # 490 K.L. Beattie, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 381)
    - # 491 David A. Jackson, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 382)
    - # 492 Hartin D. Snider: Declined, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 383)
    - # 493 Hichael Engler, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 384)
    - # 494 Brian B. Gourlie: Declined, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 385)
    - # 495 Jordan S. Paber, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 386)
    - # 496 Arthur Lockwood, 1978-1982 (Box 37, Folder 387)
    - # 497 Webster K. Cavanee, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 388)
    - # 498 Thomas H. Eickbush, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 389)
    - # 499 Lawrence Friedhoff, 1948-1980 (Box 38, Folder 390)
    - # 500 Jeffrey Garwin: Declined, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 391)
    - # 501 Gary P. Radice, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 392)
    - # 502 Nigel Stow: Declined, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 393)
    - # 503 Wayne Wecksler: Declined, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 394)
    - # 504 Roger C. Wiegand, 1978-1981 (Box 38, Folder 395)
    - # 505 Barry Schur, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 396)
    - # 506 Harvin Hendricks: Declined, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 397)
    - # 507 Martin Privalsky, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 398)
    - # 508 Patricia Bacha, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 399)
    - # 509 Susan Strome: Declined, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 400)
    - # 510 Malcolm Winkler: Declined, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 401)
    - # 511 Harry Detrich: Declined, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 402)
    - # 512 Sanford Bernstein: Declined, 1977-1980 (Box 38, Folder 403)
    - # 513 Ann Chapman, 1979-1987 (Box 39, Folder 404)
    - # 514 David Hui: Declined, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 405)
    - # 515 Leah Haimo: Declined, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 406)
    - # 516 Paul Kirschmeier: Declined, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 407)
    - # 517 Michael Boss: Declined, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 408)
    - # 518 L.A. Klobutcher: Declined, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 409)
    - # 519 Beatriz Levy-Wilson, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 410)
    - # 520 Kathryn V. Anderson: Declined, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 411)
    - # 521 Sharon Horovitch: Declined, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 412)
    - # 522 Mia Horowitz, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 413)
    - # 523 Hay-Kin Ho: Terminated, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 414)
    - # 524 Brian K. Kay, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 415)
    - # 525 Donald B. Oliver: Declined, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 416)
    - # 527 Lilly Bourguignon, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 417)
    - # 529 Glenn Horn, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 418)
    - # 530 Thomas Keller: Declined, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 419)
    - # 531 Kenneth Kreuzer, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 420)
    - # 532 Mark Conkling, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 421)
    - # 533 Pamela Maher, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 422)
    - # 534 Jonathan Tyler: Declined, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 423)
    - # 536 David G. Capco, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 424)
    - # 538 David Waxman: Declined, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 425)
    - # 539 Robin W. Yeaton, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 426)
    - # 540 Dale L. Boger, 1980-1984 (Box 40, Folder 427)
    - # 541 M.D. Walker, 1979-1982 (Box 40, Folder 428)
    - # 542 M.T. Fuller, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 429)
    - # 544 Philip W.. Early: Declined, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 430)
    - # 545 Robert W. Haile, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 431)
    - # 547 Mark Krevolin, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 432)
    - # 548 Kazuko Nishikura, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 433)
    - # 549 Richard Adler, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 434)
    - # 550 Kent W. Wilcox: Declined, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 435)
    - # 552 Patricia F. Maness, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 436)
    - # 553 William M. Gallatin: Declined, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 437)
    - # 554 Eric J. Ackerman, 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 438)
    - # 555 Jacqueline Sharon, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 439)
    - # 556 Janet L. Brandsma: Declined, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 440)
    - # 558 Clare Fearon: Declined, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 441)
    - # 559 Sekhar Mitra: Declined, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 442)
    - # 560 James Cunningham: Terminated, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 443)
    - # 561 Pamela J. Fink: Declined, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 444)
    - # 563 Amy Kenter: Declined, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 445)
    - # 564 Peter Novick: Declined, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 446)
    - # 566 Stanford J. Stevart: Declined, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 447)
    - # 570 Roger A. Daley: Declined, 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 448)
    - # 571 Eileen Lafer: Declined, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 449)
    - # 572 Timothy L. Kanser: Declined, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 450)
    - # 573 Darryl C. Rideout: Declined, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 451)